<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, your only task is to respond as quickly as possible when a stimulus appears on screen.

Each time [STIM_DESCRIPTION] appears, press the left mouse button as quickly as possible. Do not try to anticipate when a stimulus might appear - simply respond as quickly as possible when you see [STIM_DESCRIPTION].

Click the left mouse button when you are ready to begin.</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin the next part.</item>
    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">Practice trials complete. Click the left mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Click the left mouse button to exit the program.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Click the left mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to continue.</item>
    <item key="Previous Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to go back.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
  <map name="Sound">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, your only task is to respond as quickly as possible when you hear a sound.

Each time you hear [STIM_DESCRIPTION], press the left mouse button as quickly as possible. Do not try to anticipate when a sound might occur - simply respond as quickly as possible when you hear [STIM_DESCRIPTION].

Click the left mouse button when you are ready to begin.</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>