<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, you will be shown a series of visual stimuli, presented one at a time. Your only task is to respond as quickly as possible to all stimuli EXCEPT for the target stimulus. 

In this part of the experiment, the target stimulus is [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL]. Anytime [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL] appears, you should make no response.

If any other stimulus besides [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL] appears, respond by clicking the left mouse button as quickly as possible. Try to respond as quickly as possible while still being accurate.

Click the left mouse button when you are ready to begin. 
</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin the next part.</item>
    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">Practice trials complete. Click the left mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Click the left mouse button to exit the program.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Click the left mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to continue.</item>
    <item key="Previous Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to go back.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
  <map name="Sound">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, you will hear a series of sounds, presented one at a time. Your only task is to respond as quickly as possible to all sounds EXCEPT for the target sound. 

In this part of the experiment, the target sound is [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL]. Anytime you hear  [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL], you should make no response.

If you hear any other sound besides [NOGO_STIMULUS_LABEL], respond by clicking the left mouse button as quickly as possible. 

When you are ready to begin, click the left mouse button to move on. Try to respond as quickly as possible while still being accurate.</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>