<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, you will see a series of two different stimuli presented one at a time. Your task is to determine which stimulus was presented, and press the appropriate button as quickly as possible.

If you see [STIM_ONE_DESCRIPTION], press the left mouse button as quickly as possible. 

If you see [STIM_TWO_DESCRIPTION], press the right mouse button as quickly as possible.

Try not to anticipate which stimulus will appear, or when it will appear. Simply respond as quickly as possible when you see a stimulus. Remember, press the left mouse button if you see [STIM_ONE_DESCRIPTION]. Press the right mouse button if you see [STIM_TWO_DESCRIPTION].

Press either mouse button when you are ready to begin.</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Press either mouse button to begin the next part.</item>
    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Press either mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">Practice trials complete. Press either mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Press either mouse button to exit the program.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Press either mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Click the right mouse button to continue.</item>
    <item key="Previous Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to go back.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Click the right mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Click either mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
  <map name="Sound">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, you will hear a series of two sounds presented one at a time. Your task is to determine which of two possible sounds was presented, and press the appropriate button as quickly as possible.

If you hear [STIM_ONE_DESCRIPTION], press the left mouse button as quickly as possible. 

If you hear [STIM_TWO_DESCRIPTION], press the right mouse button as quickly as possible.

Try not to anticipate which sound you will hear, or when it will occur. Simply respond as quickly as possible when you hear a sound. Remember, press the left mouse button if you hear [STIM_ONE_DESCRIPTION]. Press the right mouse button if you hear [STIM_TWO_DESCRIPTION].

Press either mouse button when you are ready to begin.</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>