<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">In this task, you will use the mouse to follow, or track, a moving target.

The target is [TARGET_DESCRIPTION]. At the beginning of each trial, the target and your mouse cursor will appear in the same location. After a short delay, the target will begin to move. Use the mouse to keep your cursor on the target as much as possible, until it stops moving. Be careful! Sometimes the mouse may not move in the direction you expect. It might be hard to keep the cursor on the target, but do your best to track the target until it stops moving.

Click the left mouse button to start when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Feedback Caption">On Target:</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin the next part.</item>
    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">Practice trials complete. Click the left mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Click the left mouse button to exit the program.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Click the mouse to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to continue.</item>
    <item key="Previous Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to go back.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Click the left mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>