<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">You will be shown a series of letter strings, one at a time. Your task is to identify whether each letter string you see is a target, and to press the corresponding button.

In this experiment, the target string is: [TARGET_LETTER]. However, there is a catch. [TARGET_LETTER] should ONLY be considered a target when it follows the string [VALID_CUE_LETTER]. If [TARGET_LETTER] follows ANY other string, you should no longer consider it a target. So, for example, if you see the following sequence:

[VALID_CUE_LETTER], [TARGET_LETTER], [INVALID_CUE_LETTER], [TARGET_LETTER]

only the second string in that sequence is a target. All the other strings, including the last one, are NOT targets.

When you see a target, press the left mouse button. For any other stimuli, press the right mouse button.

Try to answer as quickly as possible while still being accurate. Press either mouse button when you are ready to begin.</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Press either mouse button to begin the next part.</item>
    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Press either mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">Practice trials complete. Press either mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Press either mouse button to exit the program.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Press either mouse button to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Click the right mouse button to continue.</item>
    <item key="Previous Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to go back.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Click the right mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Click either mouse button to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>